[Music]
ICICI Lombard is known for its technological advancements
that make processes
like booking a two-wheeler third party policy
very easy.
Welcome to this video in which we will
tell you about the steps to book a two-wheeler third party policy.
Visit the Digital Seva Portal home page and
click on the Insurance option.
Type ICICI Lombard in the search option.
Click on the ICICI Lombard icon.
Arrive at the
ICICI Lombard home page. On the right side of the home page,
you will find our product options.
Click on the WTP icon to buy a third-party bike policy.
Click on Renew Assisting and Lops Policy
and then click on the Get Full Quote red tab.
Screen One: Register Details:
Once on the WTP page,
enter your customer's vehicle registration number
and
click on the Get RTO tab to get the complete vehicle details. Check the
model, manufacture, engine and
chassis number shown on the page with your RC.
Screen Two: Vehicle Details:
PA cover has already been removed from the premium rate
and TPPD has been barred up to Rs 6000.
Previous policy details have
already been entered Click on 'No' option
to view Premium 828
Screen Three Customer Details Click on the orange coloured 'Get Code' tab
to view the customer details Enter customer
name, address, pin code, email ID and
phone number
After entering the customer details,
click on the orange tab of 'Get Proposal' to view the proposal number generated with Premium 828 At the
bottom right corner of the page, you will
find the 'Buy Policy' option in blue colour Click
on it to go to the CSC Wallet payment page
Screen Four View Policy PDF
After entering your CSC password and Wallet PIN, wait for a while
You will reach a page where you will
see your policy number and
an option to view your customer's policy PDF
[Music]